[
  {
    "question": "What are the four distinct phases for buyer behaviour?",
    "answer": "&nbsp;(1) Felt Need <br />&nbsp;(2) Pre-Purchase Activity <br />&nbsp;(3) Purchase Activity<br />&nbsp;(4) Post-Purchase Activity"
  },
  {
    "question": "The <strong>four Ps of marketing</strong> are: ",
    "answer": "product, place, price, and promotion."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the components of the <strong>promotional mix</strong>? ",
    "answer": "Personal selling, advertising, sales promotion, publicity, and public relations."
  },
  {
    "question": "Pens, gifts, calendars, and note pads are examples of ________ ________. ",
    "answer": "Pens, gifts, calendars, and note pads are examples of <strong>sales promotion</strong>."
  },
  {
    "question": "Face-to-face communication with a potential customer is known as _______ _______.",
    "answer": "Face-to-face communication with a potential customer is known as <strong>personal selling</strong>."
  },
  {
    "question": "Define <strong>niche marketing</strong>. ",
    "answer": "Niche marketing is focusing an entire marketing effort on a relatively small, but active and growing, target market."
  },
  {
    "question": "Misleading advertising or similar deception practices are dealt with in the provisions of the ________ Act.",
    "answer": "Misleading advertising or similar deception practices are dealt with in the provisions of the <strong>Competition</strong> Act."
  },
  {
    "question": "What does SMART stand for when we say that the advertising objective should be SMART?",
    "answer": "specific, measurable, achievable, relevant and timely"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the shopping behaviour model, real estate services would be a good example of a ________ good.",
    "answer": "In the shopping behaviour model, real estate services would be a good example of a <strong>shopping</strong> good."
  },
  {
    "question": "Public relations is free media coverage of the company or its products.<br />&nbsp;(1) True<br />&nbsp;(2) False",
    "answer": "Public relations is free media coverage of the company or its products.<br />&nbsp;(1) True<br />&nbsp;<strong>(2) False</strong><br />Publicity is free media coverage of the company or its products."
  },
  {
    "question": "For important transaction-related data, it is advisable to retain hard copies.<br />&nbsp;(1) True<br />&nbsp;(2) False",
    "answer": "For important transaction-related data, it is advisable to retain hard copies.<br />&nbsp;<strong>(1) True</strong><br />&nbsp;(2) False<br />Especially if they contain written notation, signatures or initials."
  },
  {
    "question": "To be effective, digital signatures must be \"unforgeable\" and therefore use a technology called _______.\"",
    "answer": "To be effective, digital signatures must be \"unforgeable\" and therefore use a technology called <strong>cryptography</strong>.\""
  },
  {
    "question": "Printers, scanners and digital cameras would be good examples of _________.",
    "answer": "Printers, scanners and digital cameras would be good examples of <strong>peripherals</strong>."
  },
  {
    "question": "A computer program designed specifically to damage or disrupt a system is known as _______.",
    "answer": "A computer program designed specifically to damage or disrupt a system is known as <strong>malware</strong>."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the <strong>Multiple Listing Service</strong>?",
    "answer": "The Multiple Listing Service provides current inventory of available properties and a history of sales in a geographic area. The purpose is to maximize property exposure for the seller and provide a high degree of accuracy of information for potential buyers."
  },
  {
    "question": "Describe <strong>email etiquette</strong>.",
    "answer": "Email etiquette includes, but is not limited to the following: answering emails prompty, avoiding grammatical errors, starting messages with a salutation, ending messages with your name, keeping messages concise, avoiding ALL CAPS, and avoid using clich&eacute; taglines."
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the <strong>internet domain</strong> \".com\" imply?",
    "answer": "\".com\" implies that the domain is meant for commercial purposes."
  },
  {
    "question": "Describe <strong>web libraries</strong>.",
    "answer": "Web libraries are websites that collect, categorize, and index large amounts of information."
  },
  {
    "question": "A _______ is an integrated collection of security measures designed to prevent unauthorized electronic access to a networked computer system.",
    "answer": "A <strong>firewall</strong> is an integrated collection of security measures designed to prevent unauthorized electronic access to a networked computer system."
  },
  {
    "question": "The ________ _________ ________ ______ regulates the way private sector organizations collect, use, keep secure and disclose personal information in BC.",
    "answer": "The <strong>Personal Information Protection Act</strong> regulates the way private sector organizations collect, use, keep secure and disclose personal information in BC."
  }
]